math-salamanders.com 2015-12-30

# Math Salamanders Privacy Policy

We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use Math Salamanders, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. 

We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us. 

**Math Salamanders** strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our website. 

Personal Information

**Math Salamanders** collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number. 

This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries. Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. 

Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties. 

Use of Cookies and Web Beacons

We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. 

The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of our site's services, a cookie enables Math Salamanders to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site. 

A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. 

They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site. 

This website will not: 

  * Share any personal information with third parties.

You can disable any cookies already stored on your computer, but these may stop our website from functioning properly. 

Using the link below open the WikiHow website in a new browser window with information about how to disable cookies. 

Third Party Advertising - Google Adsense and Infolinks

We may serve third-party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads being served on our web site to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on our web site. 

Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google, which uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google uses the DART cookie, which enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visits to this site and other sites on the Web. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting Google's ad and content network policy. 

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you so choose. 

Infolinks is an In Text advertising service; they take my text and create links within it. If you hover your mouse over these double underlined links, you will see a small dialog box containing an advertisement related to the text. You can choose to move the mouse away and go on with your browsing, or to click on the box and visit the relevant ad. 

[ Learn more or opt out of the Infolinks Double Underline Link Ads. ](http://www.infolinks.com/opt-out.html?pid=247155%20&wsid=0%20)

Search Box

The search box on this web site ("Search Box") is powered by Google Inc. ("Google"). You acknowledge and agree that Google's privacy policy (located at http://www.google.com/privacy.html) shall apply to your use of the Search Box and by using the Search Box you consent to Google using your personal data in accordance with its privacy policy. 

Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age. 

Non-Personal Information

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. 

Release of Information

If Math Salamanders is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us. 

Updates and Effective Date

**Math Salamanders** reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it. 

Agreeing to Terms

If you do not agree to Math Salamanders Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site. 

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy. 

Thank you.

The Math Salamanders 

Whether you are looking for a free Homeschool Math Worksheet collection, banks of useful Math resources for teaching kids, or simply wanting to improve your child's Math learning at home, there is something here at Math-Salamanders.com for you! 

The Math Salamanders hope you enjoy using these free printable Math worksheets and all our other Math games and resources. 

We welcome any comments about our site on the Facebook comments box at the bottom of every page. 

comments received about this page so far! 

***SOCIALIZEIT***
